wiwo.dev

- https://wiwo.dev
- https://github.com/wiwo-dev
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ wojciech-wieclawski/

Core Technologies

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- React Native
- Next.js
- Node.is
- Framer Motion
- Prisma
- Google Firestore
- HTMI
- CSS
- Tailwind CSS

Other Digital Skills

- UI/UX Design
- Figma
- Wordpress, Webflow
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Video Editing (Final Cut)
- Digital Marketing
- Google Analytics
- Social Media Management
- Data Analysis

Wojciech Więcławski

Web & Mobile Developer with digital marketing experience

I'm a developer with many years of experience in the corporate world of Digital Marketing. I am a Computer Science Engineer. My education and work experience let me understand both the technical and business sides of work. Besides coding in various technologies I also design user interfaces.

Education

Poznań University of Technology 2012-2016

Computer Science (Bachelor of Engineering)

Poznan, Poland

Kozminski University
Management in Virtual Environment (Masters)

Warsaw, Poland

Experience

Freelance Web Developer

2020-present

2016-2018

Building web pages, web applications and mobile apps. Main technologies: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, NextJS, React Native and sometimes WordPress or Webflow if needed. Designing user interfaces in Figma.

Selected projects

Auction Trackr

Project for a client. Platform with an archive of car auctions from USA. Searching, filtering, well thought out SEO and sitemaps as there is almost a million auctions in the database that is changing daily. Localisation for multiple languages with i18n.

I was responsible for the design and frontend part. API created by a backend dev.

The project is nearing completion.

Next.js 13, shadcn/ui, next-seo, next-intl, Framer Motion

Berkeley Health Mobile App

Mobile app created for Berkeley Health Limited, a leading UK provider of diagnostic rapid self-tests.

Product catalogue with PDF reader for leaflets, video instructions, users can save the medical test results inside the app, articles and health advices. All the content is pulled from an API (Django, created by a backend dev that I was collaborating with) App available in App Store and Google Play in August.

React Native, Expo

PacMan Game & Snake Game

Portfolio fun projects. I recreated two old school games. Source code and deployed versions available at wiwo.dev/projects/pacman and wiwo.dev/projects/snake-game

PacMan: Next.js, TailwindCSS, TypeScript, Framer Motion SnakeGame: React, TailwindCSS, Firebase

Sorting Algorithms Visualizer

This project is visualising how sorting algorithms work. It helps to understand each step. Users can pause the visualisation and go forward or backward step by step.

Read more: wiwo.dev/projects/sorting-visualizer

React, ChakraUI, Framer Motion

Wojciech Więcławski

Web & Mobile Developer with digital marketing experience

- https://wiwo.dev
- https://github.com/wiwo-dev
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ wojciech-wieclawski/

Wordpress and Webflow websites

Every web developer work on a project in Wodpress or Webflow from time to time. It is often the best solution for smaller businesses.

Some of my work: <u>dom-rodzinny.pl</u>, <u>loopspaces.com</u>, <u>wynajem-lodzi-ilawa.pl</u> Wordpress, Webflow, JS, PHP

Veggies & Fruits

Full stack eCommerce Platform created from scratch for learning purposes. Payments with Stripe. Admin panel with image upload (imgix). User authiorization. Read more: wiwo.dev/projects/ecommerce

NextJS, Prisma, NextAuth, Imgix, Stripe

IT, Digital Marketing and Social Media Consultant

2022-present

Developing strategies and creative communication ideas. Conducting workshops and trainings. Information technology consulting.

Red Bull

Social Media Manager	2019-2022
Digital Specialist	2016-2019
Digital Marketing Trainee	2015-2016
Student Brand Manager	2012-2015

Digital projects management. Building and developing websites, platforms, and digital experiences on redbull.com. Concept development and supervision. Coding. Cooperation with other company departments, interactive agencies and external partners in Red Bull's digital activities.

Managing a team of independent contractors and full-time employees responsible for over 20 social media profiles. Tracking and analysing users' traffic data. Planning and executing paid advertising. Preparing media plans, campaign optimisation, and ongoing control of expenses. Defining and developing social content creators and opinion leaders programs. Producing video content for social media and www.

Selected projects

Red Bull Enduro Liga - Web platform that allowed us to move sport competitions (motocross enduro) to the virtual world during the pandemic. Web App for riders to upload their video submissions. Each entry checked and assessed by the admins. Platform was connected to Discord server.

My role: project leader - cooperation with a global digital agency and multiple stakeholders, frontend developer

Red Bull Wjazd na Bramke - Esport tournament in Rocket League. Creation of a web app for team pairing, bracket generation, results submission and live result view. My role: project leader (digital part), working with global and local agencies

Red Bull Ruchome Piaski - a website about a creative volleyball tournament series. Registration form, full integration with project's Key Visual.

My role: designer & developer

....and many more digital projects that I will gladly describe during an interview.

Kitesurfing, Windsurfing and Skiing Instructor

2010-2015

Why do I add this work experience in my resume when applying for developer's position? As a former sports instructor, I offer a unique perspective to the developer's role. This experience refined my ability to communicate complex concepts effectively, making me a good knowledge sharer and presenter. Having taught diverse individuals in various countries, I possess strong communication and presentation skills that contribute positively to collaborative development projects.